[{"answer": "Well, Piers, what I think is going on is they are looking the evidence and we've always believed if they looked at the evidence, that they will hold George Zimmerman accountable for killing an unarmed teenager.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What do you make out jury so far out three and a bit hours asking for a lot of documentation, clearly prepared to go through a lot of evidence, it would seem?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, what is interesting about that, Piers, it was extremely emotional, especially for Trayvon's mother.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Because it was clearly trying to create an impression to the jury that Trayvon Martin wasn't just a kid, he was a quite strapping teenager?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "There was a moment Mark O'Mara turned his attention to you personally.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "But isn't that exactly what George Zimmerman did that night when he profiled and made assumptions about Trayvon Martin and was wrong and, unfortunately, Trayvon had to pay with his life?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "No, Ben Crump or someone like him, because had Ben Crump not gotten involved in the case, maybe for some good reasons to begin with.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you think George Zimmerman would have even been charged had Ben Crump not been pulled into this?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, you know, they seem to forget that Trayvon Martin was a dead, unarmed kid on the ground who his client profiled, followed, pursued, and shot in the heart.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Ben Crump, your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I will say it like this.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Ben Crump, always good to talk to you.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "If Trayvon Martin was in the car and profiled and followed and pursued George Zimmerman and killed him, what would the verdict be?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "When you hear Ben Crump talked like that, it's very hard to see how this jury can basically say to George Zimmerman, I think, off you go?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Yes, I think they're going to be focused on facts, obviously, their own biases, their own interpretations and their emotions are going to weigh into that.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "It's going to be powerful.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Just any human level, isn't that going to be incredibly powerful with an all-female, mother- related jury?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, I take issues with one of the points that Mr. Crump made.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, I will tell you -- one of the things I think come from this very tragic situation and I think regardless of where people sort out of what will happen, I think that we all agree that there is a tragedy this 17-year-old lost his life.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Is this a fuss?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Personally, I think stand your ground is a terrible, terrible law.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "I look at what's happened with gun control in America, where absolutely zero happened after Sandy Hook and Aurora, why should I have confidence anything will change?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I think it's an awful law.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "It's a license to kill people, isn't it?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "He's not guilty of anything but protecting his own life.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What is that, when a grown man frustrated, angry with hate in his heart gets out of his car with a loaded gun and follows a child, a stranger in the dark, and shoots him through his heart?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, I think it will make a difference -- if you look at your show over the past couple weeks, when you've had multiple women on, that have disagreement about particular topic, you can see how animated they get.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Six women, five mothers, five white mothers, women, what difference will that make do you think to the dynamic in that jury room, if anything?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Of course, they are.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "I'm also sure -- although they won't be aware of the huge attention the trial is getting on television -- they will be aware, I'm sure, before that this was potentially going to be a big story, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Let me come to Jeff --", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "I thought it was interesting with the use of force expert who -- the prosecution was cross examining him, said if Zimmerman is being straddled by Trayvon Martin, how easy would it be for him to get the gun out of his waist belt?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, the defense is that he got out of the car and then he was just assaulted.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Jeff, the point you were going to make?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I actually did.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Did you believe his story?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "I mean, if he's been -- if he's been taught this, then to leave the car is beyond his training and you got to wonder, if those jurors are thinking what happened that he actually left that car to go after Trayvon?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "You take into consideration everything you learn about an individual.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Why did you believe that so strongly?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "The main concern that you have is everybody makes the presumption that it's just a 17-year-old kid walking home.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Surely, there is another option than pulling out a gun and shooting him dead, isn't it?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "That's the problem.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Judge Hatchett?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I believe Zimmerman is guilty.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I think that to me is the most crucial point about what the public outcry was here.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Charles Blow?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "So, my question is, can the jury be truly objective?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Thanks.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Daniel?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "See, this is a great question --", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "I'm around the same age as Trayvon, and would this case be different if it was me that night instead of him?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "No, you had your chance.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Can I answer it?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "We might be debating parts of it.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "If Trayvon had been that young man, Daniel, would we be even debating this here?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "But you were not in Zimmerman's castle, right?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yes, it would.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "It would make it all so much easier, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "It can fluctuate.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Is that normally how these things work?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Do you think it was a deliberate strategy?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I don't think -- a lot of people have said that to me.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "To say, how could this guy so out of shape, he could never win a fight?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "What do you think is going to come back?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "From what I've seen, it depends on how they take Zimmerman's test -- he didn't testify, but his statements that are in part of the evidence.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "What do you think is the fair result?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "I believe that it is hard to buy his account of what happened, particularly and most importantly --", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "What do you personally think?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I think it's going to be manslaughter, and I think it will come early next week.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Judge Hatchett, very quickly, your verdict?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I think legally, it's an acquittal.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Judge Alex?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "If I were a juror, I would say not guilty based on what I seen.", "docId": "130712pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Marc?", "qSentId": 617}]